## KATIE **PINDELL**

1621 Massachusetts Ave. SE, Apt 9 Washington, D.C. · (443) 845-8008 pindellk@protonmail.com · LinkedIn · Portfolio · GitHub

I have over 5 years' experience in the federal financial consulting field and am a fledgling full stack developer. I'm able to master new technical skills quickly and thrive in environments that call for close attention to detail. I value clear, effective communication and am a proactive, solutions-oriented addition to any team.

## **SKILLS**

- Microsoft Power BI
- Microsoft and Adobe Suites
- Oracle Federal Financial System

- HTML
- CSS (Bootstrap)
- JavaScript (jQuery)

## **EXPERIENCE**

APRIL 2019 - PRESENT

## MANAGER, KEARNEY & COMPANY – ALEXANDRIA, VA

I support the Financial Management Division program component at a client agency. In this role I maintain grant budgets, track program spending, and contribute to financial reporting and analysis for the CFO and CEO offices.

JUNE 2018 - MARCH 2019

## SENIOR ASSOCIATE, KEARNEY & COMPANY - ALEXANDRIA, VA

Prepared and peer reviewed journal vouchers; prepared Office of Management and Budget (OMB) A-136 compliant quarterly financial statements; prepared monthly and quarterly financial analysis for management; prepared financial reconciliations; completed audit readiness checklists; wrote process documentation for financial management practices.

JUNE 2015 - MAY 2018

## ASSOCIATE, KEARNEY & COMPANY – ALEXANDRIA, VA

Prepared and peer reviewed journal vouchers; prepared OMB A-136 compliant quarterly financial statements; prepared quarterly financial statement variance analysis; prepared monthly and quarterly financial analysis for management; prepared financial reconciliations.

## **EDUCATION**

EXPECTED 2021

## THE CODING BOOT CAMP AT JOHNS HOPKINS ENGINEERING

Curriculum includes: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, progressive web apps, agile methodology, computer science, database theory, MongoDB, MySQL, Git

MAY 2015

# BACHELOR OF SCIENCE: ACCOUNTING, MANGEMENT THE UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA AT ASHEVILLE – ASHEVILLE. NC

GPA: 3.6, UNC Asheville Laurels Scholar Recipient, Dean's List Honors Scholar Distinction, University Research Scholar Distinction Study Abroad: Honors Semester in London, UNC Chapel Hill